Dolores Tauriello

Township of Brick, NJ 08724 deetaur.com - 908-507-5442

Office Assistant specializing in administrative support in moving company and real estate offices. Committed to delivering high quality results with very little supervision. Flexible and hardworking. Courteous and friendly.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administrative Assistant/Receptionist

CENTURY 21 VALUE PLUS REALTY - Lakewood, NJ - 2010-06 - 2017-04

Managed reception area, answered all incoming calls for inquires on availability of homes, took calls for agents, greeted clients and visitors. Handled or media and public relation inquiries. Served as a central point for all outside vendors and salespeople. Handled all office correspondence in and out, made deposits for all monies received in office and kept records for 4 accounts on Quickbooks. Handled

all account payables and receivables for office. Created new filing system, closed out all Listing and Sold files in C21 system. Entered Listings in the MLS system for agents. Worked with agents who had REO and Fannie Mae Accounts. I kept a very well organized office.

Administrative Assistant/Receptionist

COLDWELL BANKER RESIDENTIAL BROKERAGE - FLEMINTON - Fleminton, NJ - 1995-06 - 2010-01

Managed the reception area, including responding to phone calls, and greeting visitors and potential clients. Managed daily operation of all office needs including all Listing and Sales files, faxes, office correspondence and assisted agents and worked along with Office Managers. Set up for weekly meetings and took minutes and distributed information handouts for all 25 agents. Logged in all listings and and sales into CB system. Did Accounts Payable & Receivable.

Administrative Support to Secretary to Vice President of company

NELSON WESTERBERG ATLAS VAN LINES - Branchburg, NJ - 1984-09 - 1995-06

Support person to Salespersons of national accounts. Contact person for Relocation Dept. for employees being transferred by companies like AT&T, Nabisco, Este Lauder, M&M Mars and Merck. Contacted transferees to set up moving dates, packing and unpacking and special services. During move contacted transferee to be sure they were being kept informed when delivery would take place as planned. After move takes place, contact family to be sure that the move went well. Notified claims department to follow up if there were any problems or damages.

Part-time secretary/receptionist

WEICHERT REALTORS - Hillsborough, NJ - 1981-09 - 1984-06

Part time secretary and receptionist, Assisted agents in the office.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Business

West Side High School - Newark, NJ 1958-09 - 1961-06

SKILLS

Accounts Payable, Microsoft Office, MS OFFICE, Problem solver, Self directed

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS:

Meticulous attention to detail
Self directed
Professional and mature
Problem solver
Strong interpersonal skills
Microsoft Office
Accounts Payable& Receivable